  var test_name = "Go";
  var questions = [{
    question: "Does Go support operator overloading?",
    choices: ['Yes', 'No'],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },{
    question: "Which of the following is not a boolean type in Go?",
    choices: ['True', 'False', '0', 'All of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 2
  }, {
    question: "Which of the following operator increases integer value by one in Go?",
    choices: ['++', '%', '--', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 0
  }, {
   question: "Which of the following is true about break statement in Go?",
    choices: ['If you are using nested loops (i.e., one loop inside another loop), the break statement will stop the execution of the innermost loop and start executing the next line of code after the block',
              'If you are using nested loops (i.e., one loop inside another loop), the break statement will stop the execution of the outermost loop and start executing the next line of code after the block',
              'All of the above', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 0

}, {
    question: "Which of the following is correct about structures in Go?",
    choices: ['To access any member of a structure, we use the member access operator (.)', 'You would use struct keyword to define variables of structure type',
              'You can pass a structure as a function argument in very similar way as you pass any other variable or pointer', 'All of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 3
  }, {
    question: "Which of the following is correct about slices in Go?",
    choices: ['If a slice is declared with no inputs the by default, it is initialized as nil', 'length of a nil slice is 0', 'capacity of a nil slice is 0', 'All of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 3
  }, {
    question: "Which of the following is correct about type casting in Go?",
    choices: ['Type casting is a way to convert a variable from one data type to another data type',
              'If you want to store a long value into a simple integer then you can type cast long to int',
              'Both of the above', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 2
  }, {
    question: "Go supports pointer arithmetics.",
    choices: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 1
  }, {
    question: "In Go language, Pointer types are derived types.",
    choices: ['False', 'True'],
    correctAnswer: 1
  }, {
    question: "In Go language, Array types are inbuilt types.",
    choices: ['False', 'True'],
    correctAnswer: 0
  }];




document.write('<script type="text/javascript" src="../js/quiz_javascript.js"></script>');
